Guide to the Yale School of Drama Audio-Visual Recordings
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale School of Drama audio-visual recordings
1927-2013
RU 1024
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
230.6
1108 items
75,000
The materials consist of audiovisual recordings documenting productions, marketing, presentations, symposia, and events of the Yale School of Drama and the Yale Repertory Theatre.
Yale School of Drama
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 22-H (YRG 22-H), Photographs, audiovisual materials, and memorabilia documenting the Yale School of Drama.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The materials were transferred from the Drama Library, 2006-2008; School of Drama, 2009-2010 and 2013.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged by accession, thereunder by production name.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of audiovisual recordings documenting productions, marketing, presentations, symposia, and events of the Yale School of Drama and the Yale Repertory Theatre.
Acting -- Study and teaching; College theater; Drama -- Study and teaching; Lectures and lecturing; Repertory theater; Audiotapes; Motion pictures (visual works); Videotapes; Yale Repertory Theatre; Yale School of Drama; Yale University -- Curricula
- Audiovisual recordings of productions, presentations, and events, Circa 1937-1997; Accession 2007-A-103
  Conditions Governing Access
  Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
  - [#101429], undated; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 1)
  - 12th Night radio spot
    - Stereo, 1995 January 18; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 2)
    - Mono, 1995 January 18; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 3)
  - 17th Century Acting, undated; film reel (16mm) (Box 4)
  - Yale Repertory Theatre promos, 1986-1987; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
  - Yale Repertory Theatre promos, 1987-1988; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - Yale Repertory Theatre radio spots, 1988-1989; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 7)
  - 40th Anniversary Yale Drama School, 1965 November 6; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 8–9)
  - Acting, undated; film reel (16mm) (Box 10)
  - Acting the 17th Century Comedy, undated; film reel (16mm) (Box 11)
  - Agamemnon, Undated; film reel (16mm) (Box 12)
  - All Things Chicken, 1997 November 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 100)
  - All's Well That Ends Well, 1990 March 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 101)
  - American Gothic, Circa 1993; videotape (VHS) (Box 102)
  - American Passenger, 1995; 2 (Box 103–104)
  - Aristophanes' Lysistrata!, 1965 May 4; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 13)
  - As You Like It, 1989 May 6; 2 (Box 105–106)
  - Barrault, J. L., speech and scenes, 1967 December 9; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 14)
  - Belladonna, 1988 December; videotape (VHS) (Box 107)
  - Belle Laide, 1993 May; videotape (VHS) (Box 108)
  - The Belle of Amherst, 1990 March 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 109)
  - Billy and Dago, 1988 December; 1 (Box 107)
  - Bloody Poetry, 1996; videotape (VHS) (Box 111)
  - "Briss" by Roger L. Simon and Ed Pomerantz, Undated; film reel (16mm) (Box 15)
  - Brustein, Robert, Dean of Yale School of Drama, 1967 September 13; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 16)
  - Cabin 12, 1989 December 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 112)
  - Cannibals, 1989 October 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 113)
  - Chagall, Marc talk at Yale, 1967 February 11; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 17)
  - Charnel House Cha-Cha, 1991 October 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 114)
  - The Checker ? Heart, 1 (Box 18)
  - Cloud Nine, 1996; videotape (VHS) (Box 115)
  - The Colored Museum radio spot, 1992 November 12; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 19)
  - The Convert, 1990 May 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 116)
  - Crazythirst, 1994 April 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 117)
  - Danton's Breath, 1995; videotape (VHS) (Box 118)
  - The Darkroom Comedy, Undated; film reel (16mm) (Box 20)
  - Dead Wall Revery, 1988 December; videotape (VHS) (Box 119)
  - Devices, Circa 1980s; videotape (VHS) (Box 120)
  - Directing, Undated; 2 (Box 21–22)
  - Diva Studies, 1996 May 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 121)
  - Don Juan, 1993 January 30; 2 (Box 122–123)
  - Don Juan's Secret Daughter, 1993 December; videotape (VHS) (Box 124)
  - A Dose of Durang, 1996; videotape (VHS) (Box 125)
  - Dreams Are Toys, 1990 October; videotape (VHS) (Box 126)
  - Dynamite Tonight
    - Rehearsal tape, piano and voice, 1966 October 21; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 89)
    - War, original, 1966 October 21; film reel (16mm) (Box 90)
    - War general and ind?, original, 1966 October 21; film reel (16mm) (Reel 91)
    - 1966 October 21, 7 (Reel 92–98)
    - Film credits, 35 mm negatives, 1966 October 21 (Box 99)
    - Audiotape (reel-to-reel), Undated (Box 23)
  - Elm Street 8, 1948 March; film reel (16mm) (Box 24)
  - Endgame
    - Symposium following first performance (featuring Gordon Rogoff, Andre Gregory, and John Gassner), 1966 September 20; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 25)
    - Symposium following second performance (featuring Andre Gregory, Robert Brustein, and Arnold Weinstein), 1966 September 21; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 26)
    - Symposium following third performance (featuring Gordon Rogoff, Andre Gregory, and Erich Segal), 1966 September 22; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 27)
    - Symposium following fourth performance (featuring Andre Gregory and Rochelle Owens), 1966 September 23; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 28)
    - Symposium following fifth performance (featuring Andre Gregory and John Gassner), 1966 September 24; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 29)
  - Faithful, 1996; videotape (VHS) (Box 127)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes Fox 61 interview and review.
  - Fatzer (edited -Berlin, London, USA), Undated; videotape (U-matic) (Box 30)
  - Founder, 1988 December; videotape (VHS) (Box 128)
  - Fuentes Ovejuna, 1992-1993; videotape (VHS) (Box 129)
  - Garroway at Large, Undated; film reel (16mm) (Box 31)
  - God Bless, Undated; film reel (16mm) (Box 32)
  - Good Person of Szechwan, Circa 1980s; 2 (Box 130–131)
  - The Great Highway, Circa 1980s; 2 (Box 132–133)
  - Hamlet, 1988 January; 2 (Box 134–135)
    There are intermittent issues with the sound on the video cassette, Box 135.
  - Happy End, Circa 1980s; videotape (VHS) (Box 136)
  - Harrison, J. and M. Lowey, "Theatre Arts and the Foundations", 1961 August 29; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 33)
  - Henry IV, Undated; film reel (16mm) (Box 34)
  - He Who Must Die, 1961; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 35–38)
  - The Human Figure in Motion, 1996 January 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 207)
  - If Only, 1996; videotape (VHS) (Box 127)
  - In Arcadia, 1997 May 1-3; videotape (VHS) (Box 137)
  - Ivanov, undated; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 39)
  - It's Not All Play, 1937; 4 (Box 40–43)
  - JBB
    - Act I, 1960 March 23; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 44)
    - Act I -begin Act II, 1960 March 23; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 45)
    - Act II, 1960 March 23; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 46)
    - Act II (end), 1960 March 23; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 47)
  - Jones, James Earl, Yale Repertory Theatre promo, Undated; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 48)
  - [Jones, Walter], 1975 April 30; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 49–50)
  - King Lear, 1996; videotape (VHS) (Box 138)
  - Lady from the Sea, 1995; videotape (VHS) (Box 139)
  - The Land Claim, 1994 February 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 140)
  - Lenses, Undated; film reel (16mm) (Box 51)
  - The Lesson, 1990 November 17; videotape (VHS) (Box 141)
  - Linbergh, 1990 April 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 142)
  - The Love of Don Perlimplin for Belissa, 1990 September 20; videotape (VHS) (Box 141)
  - Ludlow Fair, 1989 December 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 143)
  - Macbeth
    - Music -Arthur Rubinstein, 1961 January; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 52)
    - 1971, 1 (Box 53)
    - Undated, 2 (Box 54–55)
    - Videotape (VHS), Circa 1980s (Box 144)
  - Man Better Man, 1962 January 24; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 56–57)
  - Mary Kay Medea, Circa 1980s; videotape (VHS) (Box 144)
  - Mask Making, Undated; 2 (Box 58–59)
  - Measure for Measure, 1991 October 25; 2; There is a tension problem with the video cassette (Box 145–146)
  - Medea, 1987-1988; 2 (Box 147–148)
  - Medicine Men, 1990 October; videotape (VHS) (Box 149)
  - Merchant of Venice, 1993 February 13-15; videotape (VHS) (Box 150)
  - Mississippi Nude
    - Videotape (VHS), 1989 December 4 (Box 151)
    - 2 videotapes (VHS), 1989-1990 (Box 152–153)
  - The Most Lamentable Tragedy of Titus Andronicus, 1989 September; 2 (Box 154–155)
  - The Night of the Iguana, 1990 April 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 156)
  - Nora, 1990 April 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 157)
  - Not All Play, Undated; film reel (16mm) (Box 60)
  - Oenslager, David, lectures and talks
    - Speech about Robert Edward Jones, 1971 May 3; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 61)
    - Speech about Edward Gordon Craig, 1971 May 3; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 62)
    - On his theatrical experiences; advise to designers", Undated; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 63–64)
  - Oleanna
    - Copy 1, 1993 September 29; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 65)
    - Copy 2, 1993 September 29; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 66)
  - One True Thing, 1989 December 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 158)
  - Oriki of a Grasshopper, 1995; videotape (VHS) (Box 159)
  - The Ostrich, 1988 December; videotape (VHS) (Box 119)
  - Oxford Fatzer (copy II), 1979 March; videotape (U-matic) (Box 67)
  - Oxford Fatzer (tape II USA), Undated; videotape (U-matic) (Box 68)
  - Peer Gynt, 1994 April 29; 2 (Box 160–161)
  - Pericles
    - 3 videoatpes (VHS), 1988-1989 (Box 162–164)
    - 2 videotapes (VHS), 1995 March 31 (Box 165–166)
  - The Piano Lesson, 1995 February 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 167)
  - Polar Flight, 1991 April; videotape (VHS) (Box 168)
  - Pompeii, 1991 February 23; 2 (Box 169–170)
  - Richard III, 1990 February 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 171)
  - The Ride Across Lake Constance, 1997 March 11-15; videotape (VHS) (Box 172)
  - Sainte Carmen of the Main, 1988-1989; 2 (Box 173–174)
  - Save the Tilt-A-Whirl, 1989 Fall; videotape (VHS) (Box 175)
  - Schrock, J. Gladden, "Dogstar"; Keith Fowler's Thesis; selected sound effects, Circa 1963; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 69)
  - Seagull
    - Cast I, 1988 February; 2 (Box 176–177)
    - Cast II, 1988 February; 2 (Box 178–179)
    - Cast III, 1988 February 5; 2 (Box 180–181)
    - 2 videotapes (VHS), 1997 November (Box 182–183)
  - Seminar held at Alumni Theatre Day (featuring Robert Brustein, Howard Stein, Jeremy Geidt, Ariel Ballif, and Gordon Rogoff), 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel), 1968 May 18 (Box 70–72)
  - The Size of the World, 1989 November 20; videotape (VHS) (Box 184)
  - Sontag, Susan, Critique of the (Euripides), 1967 January 15; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 73)
  - Skeletons, 1989 November 18; 2 (Box 185–186)
  - South Road Down, 1990 November 16; 1 (Box 187)
  - Stamford Fatzer (edited USA copy), Undated; videotape (U-matic) (Box 74)
  - Sutter's Field, 1997 Spring; videotape (VHS) (Box 188)
  - The Swan, 1993 January 18-30; videotape (VHS) (Box 189)
  - Tagore, Rabindranath, Natir Puja, Undated; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 75)
  - Taylor, Harold, AETA address, 1963 August 26; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 76)
  - Telenews Daily, 1949 December 8; film reel (16mm) (Box 77)
  - The Tempest
    - Videotape (VHS), 1989 October 27 (Box 191)
    - Videotape (VHS), 1990 December (Box 192)
  - Three Sisters
    - 2 videotapes (VHS), 1986-1987 (Box 193–194)
    - (tape 2 only), 1994 October 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 195)
  - Three Weeks After Marriage, 1996; videotape (VHS) (Box 125)
  - Through the Leaves, 1996; videotape (VHS) (Box 196)
  - T.O.Y.L., 1968 May 18; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 78)
  - Tumbling After, 1993 May 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 197)
  - Twelfth Night, 1990 October 25; 2 (Box 198–199)
  - Uncle Vanya, 1988-1989; 2 (Box 200–201)
  - [Unidentified], Undated; 2 (Box 79–80)
  - [Unidentified], Undated; film reel (16mm) (Box 81)
  - Unmerciful Good Fortune, 1992 October; videotape (VHS) (Box 202)
  - Victory source test, 1974 November 5; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 82)
  - Waiting for Godot, 1995 March 10; 2 (Box 203–204)
  - War Play, 1988 December; videotape (VHS) (Box 128)
  - Weights and Measures, 1994 April 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 205)
  - Winterfest, Yale Repertory Theatre promo, 1988-1989; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 83)
  - World Without End, 1989 April; videotape (VHS) (Box 206)
  - Yale Device Course, Undated; film reel (16mm) (Box 84)
  - Yale-ABC Conference on drama on TV
    - Opening dinner (Professors Cole and Davison), broadcast quality, 1966 June 27; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 85)
    - Opening dinner (Professors Cole and Davison), dub, 1966 June 27; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 86)
    - Report of the conference group leaders (David Davison: chairman, Irwin S. Fox, David Susskind, and Jacqueline Babbin), 1966 June 29; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 87)
    - Report of the conference group leaders (David Davison: chairman, Irwin S. Fox, David Susskind, and Jacqueline Babbin), dub, 1966 June 29; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 88)
  - Zebra Mussels, circa 1980s; videotape (VHS) (Box 144)
- Audiorecordings of performances, 1968-1990; Accession 2008-A-112
  - 1913, 1971-1972; 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 1–3)
    - Use copy for boxes 1-3 (part 1), audiocassette (Box 1U)
    - Use copy for boxes 1-3 (part 2), audiocassette (Box 2U)
  - The 1940s Radio Hour, 1984-1985; 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 472–474)
    - Use copy for boxes 472-474 (part 1), audiocassette (Box 472U)
    - Use copy for boxes 472-474 (part 2), audiocassette (Box 473U)
  - Ah, Wilderness, 1987-1988; 2 (Box 25–26)
  - Alcestis, 1971-1972; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 27–28)
    - Use copy (part 1), audiocassette (Box 27U)
    - Use copy (part 2), audiocassette (Box 28U)
  - Alcestis, 1977-1978; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 29–32)
    - Use copy for boxes 29-32 (part 1), audiocassette (Box 29U)
    - Use copy for boxes 29-32 (part 2), audiocassette (Box 30U)
  - The Alchemist", 1972-1973; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 475–476)
    - Use copy (part 1), audiocassette (Box 475U)
    - Use copy (part 2), audiocassette (Box 476U)
  - The Alchemist", 1988; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 477–478)
    - Use copy, audiocassette (part 1) (Box 477U)
    - Use copy, audiocassette (part 2) (Box 478U)
  - Almost by Chance: Elizabeth I, 1986-1987; 2 (Box 33–34)
  - Are You Now or Have You Ever Been, 1972-1973; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 35–39)
    - Use copy for boxes 35-39 (part 1), audiocassette (Box 35U)
    - Use copy for boxes 35-39 (part 2), audiocassette (Box 36U)
    - Use copy for boxes 35-39 (part 3), audiocassette (Box 37U)
  - As I Lay Dying, 1981-1982; 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 40–41, Box 727)
    - Use copy for boxes 40-41 and 727 (part 1), audiocassette (Box 40U)
    - Use copy for boxes 40-41 and 727 (part 2), audiocassette (Box 41U)
  - As You Like It, 1978-1979; 6 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 42–47)
    - Use copy for boxes 42-47 (part 1), audiocassette (Box 42U)
    - Use copy for boxes 42-47 (part 2), audiocassette (Box 43U)
    - Use copy for boxes 42-47 (part 3), audiocassette (Box 44U)
  - Baal, 1972-1973; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 48–51)
    - Use copy for boxes 48-51 (part 1), audiocassette (Box 48U)
    - Use copy for boxes 48-51 (part 2), audiocassette (Box 49U)
  - Baal, 1981-1982; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 52–55)
    - Use copy for boxes 52-55 (part 1), audiocassette (Box 52U)
    - Use copy for boxes 52-55 (part 2), audiocassette (Box 53U)
  - The Bacchai, 1980-1981; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 479–482)
    - Use copy for boxes 479-482 (part 1), audiocassette (Box 479U)
    - Use copy for boxes 479-482 (part 2), audiocassette (Box 480U)
  - The Balcony, 1973-1974; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 483–487)
    - Use copy for boxes 483-487, 3 (Box 483U–485U)
  - Banquet Years, Undated; 2 (Box 56–57)
  - The Banquet Years, Undated; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 488–492)
  - Bartholomew Faire, 1974-1975; 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 58–60)
    - Use copy for boxes 58-60, 2 (Box 58U–59U)
  - The Bathhouse, 1984-1985; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 493–494)
    - Use copy, 2 (Box 493U–494U)
  - The Beach, 1988-1989; 2 (Box 495–496)
  - Beef, No Chicken, 1981-1982; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 61–64, Box 728)
    - Use copy for boxes 61-64 and 728, 3 audiocassettes (Box 61U–63U)
  - Between East and West, 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 65–66)
    - Use copy, 2 (Box 65U–66U)
  - Bingo, Scenes of Money and Death, 1975-1976; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 67–70)
    - Use copy for boxes 67-70, 2 (Box 67U–68U)
  - Blood Knot, 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 71–72)
  - Blood Wedding, 1983-1984; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 73–76)
    - Use copy for boxes 73-76, 2 (Box 73U–74U)
  - Boesman and Lena, 1980-1981; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 77–80)
    - Use copy for boxes 77-80, 2 (Box 77U–78U)
  - Bosoms and Neglect, 1979-1980; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 81–85)
    - Use copy for boxes 81-85, 3 (Box 81U–83U)
  - Bourgeois Gentlemen, 1972-1973; 2 (Box 86–87)
  - The Bourgeois Gentlemen, 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 497–499, Box 734–735)
  - Boys from Syracuse, 1970-1971; 2 (Box 88–89)
  - The Boys from Syracuse, 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 500–503)
  - A Break in the Skin, 1972-1973; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 4–7)
    - Use copy for boxes 4-7, 2 (Box 4U–5U)
  - The Bundle, 1972-1973; 6 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 504–509)
    - Use copy for boxes 504-509, 3 (Box 504U–506U)
  - Buried Child, 1978-1979; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 90–93)
    - Use copy for boxes 90-93, 2 (Box 90U–91U)
  - A Child's Tale, audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 8)
    - Use copy, audiocassette (Box 8U)
  - Chopin in Space, 1983-1984; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 94–95)
    - Use copy for boxes 94-95, audiocassette (Box 94U)
  - Chronicles of Hell, 1970-1971; 2 (Box 96–97)
  - The Chronicles of Hell, 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 510–512)
  - Chute Roosters, 1987-1988; audiocassette (Box 98)
  - Cock-a-Doodle-Dandy, 1973-1974; 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 99–101)
    - Use copy for boxes 99-101, 2 (Box 99U–100U)
  - The Complete Works, audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 513)
    - Use copy, audiocassette (Box 513U)
  - Crazy from the Heart, 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 102–104)
  - Curse of the Starving Class, 1979-1980; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 105–108)
    - Use copy for boxes 105-108, 2 (Box 105U–106U)
  - Dark Pony and Reunion, 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 109–111)
  - Darkroom, 1973-1974; 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 112–114)
    - Use copy for boxes 112-114, 2 (Box 112U–113U)
  - The Day of the Picnic, 1983-1984; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 514–517)
    - Use copy for boxes 514-517, 2 (Box 514U–515U)
  - Death Comes to Us All, Mary Agnes, 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel), 1974-1975 (Box 115–117)
    - Use copy for boxes 115-117, audiocassette (Box 115U)
  - A Doll House, 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 9–10)
  - Domestic Issues, 1980-1981; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 118–121)
    - Use copy for boxes 118-121, 2 (Box 118U–119U)
  - Don Juan, 1975-1976; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 122–125)
    - Use copy for boxes 122-125, 2 (Box 122U–123U)
  - Donner, 1970-1971; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 126–130)
    - Use copy for boxes 126-130, 3 (Box 126U–128U)
  - Doubt and Resolution, 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 131–134)
    - Use copy for boxes 131-134, 2 (Box 131U–132U)
  - Drums in the Night, 7 audiotapes (reel-to-reel), 1979-1980 (Box 135–140, Box 729)
    - Use copy for boxes 135-140 and 729, 2 audiocassette (Box 135U–136U)
  - The Duchess of Malfi, 1975-1976; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 518–522)
    - Use copy for boxes 518-522, 3 (Box 518U–520U)
  - Durango Flash, 1976-1977; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 141–145)
    - Use copy for boxes 141-145, 4 (Box 141U–144U)
  - Dynamite Tonight!, 1975-1976; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 146–149)
    - Use copy for boxes 146-149, 2 (Box 146U–147U)
  - Earth Spirit, 1976-1977; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 150–154)
    - Use copy for boxes 150-154, 3 (Box 150U–152U)
  - Edward II, 1973-1974; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 155–159)
    - Use copy for boxes 155-159, 3 (Box 155U–157U)
  - Emlyn Williams as Charles Dickens, 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 160–163)
    - Use copy for boxes 160-163, 2 (Box 160U–161U)
  - Emlyn Williams as Dylan Thomas Growing Up, 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 164–166)
    - Use copy for boxes 164-166, 2 (Box 164U–165U)
  - Euripides at Bay, 1977-1978; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 167–171)
    - Use copy for boxes 167-171, 3 (Box 167U–169U)
  - The Father, 1974-1975; 6 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 523–527, Box 738)
    - Use copy for boxes 523-527 and 738, 3 audiocassettes (Box 523U–525U)
  - Faulkner's Bicycle, 1984-1985; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 175–176)
    - Use copy, 2 (Box 175U–176U)
  - Feifferness, 1984-1985; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 177)
    - Use copy, audiocassette (Box 177U)
  - Fences, undated; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 178–179)
    - Use copy, 2 (Box 178U–179U)
  - Flash Floods, Undated; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 180–184)
    - Use copy for boxes 180-184, audiocassette (Box 180U)
  - The Frogs, 1973-1974; 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 528–530)
    - Use copy for boxes 528-530, 4 (Box 528U–529U, Box 530UA–530UB)
  - Geography of a Horse Dreamer, 1973-1974; 6 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 185–190)
    - Use copy for boxes 185-190, 3 (Box 185U–187U)
  - The Ghost Sonata, 1977-1978; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 531–535)
    - Use copy for boxes 531-535, 3 (Box 531U–533U)
  - Gilgamesh, 1970-1971; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 191–192)
    - Use copy for boxes 191-192, audiocassette (Box 191U)
  - God's Smoke, 1979-1980; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 193–196)
    - Use copy for boxes 193-196, 2 (Box 193U–194U)
  - Going Over, 1981-1982; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 197–198)
    - Use copy, 2 (Box 197U–198U)
  - Hamlet, Prince of California, 1989-1990; 3 (Box 199–201)
  - Hamlet, Ruth Lesser, Undated (Box 739)
  - Happy End, 1974-1975; 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 202–204)
    - Use copy for boxes 202-204, 2 audiocassette (Box 202U–203U)
  - Heat, 1971-1972; 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 205, Box 730–731)
    - Use copy for boxes 205 and 730-731, audiocassette (Box 730U)
  - Hedda Gabler, 1980-1981; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 206–210)
    - Use copy for boxes 206-210, 3 (Box 206U–208U)
  - Hello and Goodbye, 1982-1983; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 211–212)
    - Use copy for boxes 211-212, audiocassette (Box 211U)
  - Henry IV, 1976-1977; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 213–216)
    - Use copy for boxes 213-216, 2 (Box 213U–214U)
  - The Hostage, 1983-1984; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 536–540)
    - Use copy for boxes 536-540, 3 (Box 536U–538U)
  - The Idiots Karanozov, 1974-1975; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 541–544)
    - Use copy for boxes 541-544, 2 (Box 541U–542U)
  - In Good King Charles' Golden Days, 1971-1972; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 217–220)
    - Use copy for boxes 217-220, 2 (Box 217U–218U)